{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, S, H, O and directed edges K->O, S->O, K->H, H->O, S->H, K->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "33847625", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path S->O<-H.", "answer": "[set(), {'K'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, S, H, O and directed edges K->O, S->O, K->H, H->O, S->H, K->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "33847625", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path S->O<-H.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, S, H, O and directed edges K->O, S->O, K->H, H->O, S->H, K->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "33847625", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path K->S->O<-H be blocked by nodeset {'S'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, S, H, O and directed edges K->O, S->O, K->H, H->O, S->H, K->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "33847625", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path K->H<-S?\nA. set()\nB. {'O'}\nC. {'H', 'O'}\nD. {'H'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, D, U, F and directed edges V->U, U->F, D->U, V->F, V->D, D->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "51186770", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path V->D->F<-U.", "answer": "[set(), {'D'}, {'D', 'F'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, D, U, F and directed edges V->U, U->F, D->U, V->F, V->D, D->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "51186770", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path V->D->F<-U.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, D, U, F and directed edges V->U, U->F, D->U, V->F, V->D, D->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "51186770", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path U<-V->D->F be blocked by nodeset {'D'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, D, U, F and directed edges V->U, U->F, D->U, V->F, V->D, D->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "51186770", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path V->U<-D?\nA. {'U'}\nB. set()\nC. {'F', 'U'}\nD. {'F'}", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, W, N, H and directed edges W->N, N->H, Z->H, W->H, Z->W, Z->N.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "37881010", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path N<-Z->W->H.", "answer": "[{'Z'}, {'W'}, {'Z', 'W'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, W, N, H and directed edges W->N, N->H, Z->H, W->H, Z->W, Z->N.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "37881010", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path N<-Z->W->H.", "answer": "{'Z'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, W, N, H and directed edges W->N, N->H, Z->H, W->H, Z->W, Z->N.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "37881010", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path Z->N->H<-W be blocked by nodeset {'H', 'N'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, W, N, H and directed edges W->N, N->H, Z->H, W->H, Z->W, Z->N.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "37881010", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path Z->N<-W?\nA. {'H', 'N'}\nB. set()\nC. {'H'}\nD. {'N'}", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, V, C, G, Z and directed edges C->G, G->Z, V->Z, V->G, N->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "08322039", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path V->Z<-G.", "answer": "[set(), {'C'}, {'N'}, {'C', 'N'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, V, C, G, Z and directed edges C->G, G->Z, V->Z, V->G, N->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "08322039", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path V->Z<-G.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, V, C, G, Z and directed edges C->G, G->Z, V->Z, V->G, N->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "08322039", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path C->G<-V->Z be blocked by nodeset {'G', 'N'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, V, C, G, Z and directed edges C->G, G->Z, V->Z, V->G, N->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "08322039", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path C->G->Z?\nA. {'G', 'N'}\nB. {'V', 'N'}\nC. {'N'}\nD. {'V'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, L, D, U, Y and directed edges L->U, F->L, L->D, F->U, D->Y, F->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "44924149", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path F->L->D->Y.", "answer": "[{'D'}, {'L'}, {'D', 'L'}, {'D', 'U'}, {'L', 'U'}, {'D', 'L', 'U'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, L, D, U, Y and directed edges L->U, F->L, L->D, F->U, D->Y, F->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "44924149", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path F->L->D->Y.", "answer": "{'D'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, L, D, U, Y and directed edges L->U, F->L, L->D, F->U, D->Y, F->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "44924149", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path F->U<-L be blocked by nodeset {'Y'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, L, D, U, Y and directed edges L->U, F->L, L->D, F->U, D->Y, F->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "44924149", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path F->D<-L->U?\nA. {'Y'}\nB. {'D', 'Y'}\nC. {'D'}\nD. set()", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, B, O, W, Z and directed edges E->B, E->Z, B->W, E->W, W->Z, E->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "04394897", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path E->Z<-W<-B.", "answer": "[set(), {'W'}, {'O'}, {'Z', 'W'}, {'W', 'O'}, {'Z', 'W', 'O'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, B, O, W, Z and directed edges E->B, E->Z, B->W, E->W, W->Z, E->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "04394897", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path E->Z<-W<-B.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, B, O, W, Z and directed edges E->B, E->Z, B->W, E->W, W->Z, E->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "04394897", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path E->B->W->Z be blocked by nodeset {'B', 'W', 'O'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, B, O, W, Z and directed edges E->B, E->Z, B->W, E->W, W->Z, E->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "04394897", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path E->B->W?\nA. {'B', 'O'}\nB. {'O'}\nC. {'Z'}\nD. {'Z', 'O'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, L, C, D, K, M and directed edges L->D, L->M, B->L, K->M, B->K, C->M, L->C, C->D, L->K, D->K, C->K, B->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "68039197", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path L<-B->K->M<-C.", "answer": "[set(), {'D'}, {'B'}, {'K'}, {'M', 'B'}, {'M', 'K'}, {'D', 'B'}, {'D', 'K'}, {'B', 'K'}, {'M', 'D', 'B'}, {'M', 'D', 'K'}, {'M', 'B', 'K'}, {'D', 'B', 'K'}, {'M', 'D', 'B', 'K'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, L, C, D, K, M and directed edges L->D, L->M, B->L, K->M, B->K, C->M, L->C, C->D, L->K, D->K, C->K, B->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "68039197", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path L<-B->K->M<-C.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, L, C, D, K, M and directed edges L->D, L->M, B->L, K->M, B->K, C->M, L->C, C->D, L->K, D->K, C->K, B->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "68039197", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path B->D->K<-L->C->M be blocked by nodeset set()?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, L, C, D, K, M and directed edges L->D, L->M, B->L, K->M, B->K, C->M, L->C, C->D, L->K, D->K, C->K, B->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "68039197", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path K<-L->M?\nA. {'L', 'C', 'B'}\nB. {'D'}\nC. {'D', 'C', 'B'}\nD. {'C', 'B'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, O, I, S, G, T and directed edges I->G, I->S, Z->G, G->T, O->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "74423004", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path I->G->T.", "answer": "[{'G'}, {'G', 'Z'}, {'G', 'S'}, {'G', 'O'}, {'G', 'Z', 'S'}, {'G', 'Z', 'O'}, {'G', 'S', 'O'}, {'G', 'Z', 'S', 'O'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, O, I, S, G, T and directed edges I->G, I->S, Z->G, G->T, O->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "74423004", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path I->G->T.", "answer": "{'G'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, O, I, S, G, T and directed edges I->G, I->S, Z->G, G->T, O->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "74423004", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path O->I->G be blocked by nodeset {'I', 'Z', 'S', 'T'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, O, I, S, G, T and directed edges I->G, I->S, Z->G, G->T, O->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "74423004", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path O->I->G->T?\nA. {'S'}\nB. {'I', 'Z', 'G'}\nC. {'Z', 'S'}\nD. {'Z'}", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes L, K, R, C, Y, U and directed edges C->Y, C->U, R->Y, L->C, R->C, L->R, L->U, K->R, K->C, Y->U, L->K.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "99746588", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path R->Y<-C<-K<-L->U.", "answer": "[set(), {'L'}, {'C'}, {'K'}, {'L', 'Y'}, {'C', 'Y'}, {'K', 'Y'}, {'L', 'C'}, {'L', 'K'}, {'C', 'K'}, {'L', 'C', 'Y'}, {'L', 'K', 'Y'}, {'C', 'K', 'Y'}, {'L', 'C', 'K'}, {'L', 'C', 'K', 'Y'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes L, K, R, C, Y, U and directed edges C->Y, C->U, R->Y, L->C, R->C, L->R, L->U, K->R, K->C, Y->U, L->K.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "99746588", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path R->Y<-C<-K<-L->U.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes L, K, R, C, Y, U and directed edges C->Y, C->U, R->Y, L->C, R->C, L->R, L->U, K->R, K->C, Y->U, L->K.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "99746588", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path L->U<-Y<-R->C be blocked by nodeset {'K', 'U', 'Y'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes L, K, R, C, Y, U and directed edges C->Y, C->U, R->Y, L->C, R->C, L->R, L->U, K->R, K->C, Y->U, L->K.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "99746588", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path L->C<-R<-K?\nA. {'C', 'U'}\nB. {'U', 'Y'}\nC. {'R'}\nD. {'C'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, Q, J, E, G, N, T and directed edges E->T, E->N, Q->J, G->T, F->T, G->N, F->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "94842928", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path E->T<-G->N.", "answer": "[set(), {'G'}, {'Q'}, {'J'}, {'F'}, {'G', 'Q'}, {'J', 'G'}, {'G', 'F'}, {'G', 'T'}, {'J', 'Q'}, {'F', 'Q'}, {'J', 'F'}, {'J', 'G', 'Q'}, {'G', 'F', 'Q'}, {'G', 'T', 'Q'}, {'J', 'G', 'F'}, {'J', 'G', 'T'}, {'G', 'F', 'T'}, {'J', 'F', 'Q'}, {'J', 'G', 'F', 'Q'}, {'J', 'G', 'T', 'Q'}, {'G', 'F', 'T', 'Q'}, {'J', 'G', 'F', 'T'}, {'G', 'Q', 'J', 'F', 'T'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, Q, J, E, G, N, T and directed edges E->T, E->N, Q->J, G->T, F->T, G->N, F->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "94842928", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path E->T<-G->N.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, Q, J, E, G, N, T and directed edges E->T, E->N, Q->J, G->T, F->T, G->N, F->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "94842928", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path G->N<-E->T be blocked by nodeset {'J', 'N'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, Q, J, E, G, N, T and directed edges E->T, E->N, Q->J, G->T, F->T, G->N, F->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "94842928", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path E->N<-G->T?\nA. {'N'}\nB. {'J', 'F', 'N'}\nC. {'G', 'Q'}\nD. {'F', 'N', 'Q'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, A, D, C, H, R, W and directed edges J->H, D->C, J->W, C->R, A->D, A->H, D->R.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "15987908", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path A->D->C->R.", "answer": "[{'D'}, {'C'}, {'D', 'H'}, {'D', 'W'}, {'D', 'J'}, {'D', 'C'}, {'H', 'C'}, {'W', 'C'}, {'J', 'C'}, {'D', 'H', 'W'}, {'D', 'H', 'J'}, {'D', 'H', 'C'}, {'D', 'W', 'J'}, {'D', 'W', 'C'}, {'D', 'C', 'J'}, {'H', 'W', 'C'}, {'J', 'H', 'C'}, {'J', 'W', 'C'}, {'D', 'H', 'W', 'J'}, {'D', 'H', 'W', 'C'}, {'D', 'H', 'C', 'J'}, {'D', 'W', 'J', 'C'}, {'J', 'H', 'W', 'C'}, {'D', 'H', 'W', 'J', 'C'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, A, D, C, H, R, W and directed edges J->H, D->C, J->W, C->R, A->D, A->H, D->R.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "15987908", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path A->D->C->R.", "answer": "{'D'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, A, D, C, H, R, W and directed edges J->H, D->C, J->W, C->R, A->D, A->H, D->R.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "15987908", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path C<-D->R be blocked by nodeset {'A'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, A, D, C, H, R, W and directed edges J->H, D->C, J->W, C->R, A->D, A->H, D->R.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "15987908", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path A->D->R<-C?\nA. {'R'}\nB. {'J', 'H', 'R'}\nC. {'D', 'H', 'J', 'R'}\nD. {'J', 'H', 'W', 'R'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, M, B, X, N, V, J and directed edges G->X, G->V, B->V, N->J, M->N, M->B, G->N, G->M, B->X, M->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "14558094", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path G->V<-B<-M->N.", "answer": "[set(), {'B'}, {'M'}, {'X'}, {'J'}, {'M', 'B'}, {'X', 'B'}, {'V', 'B'}, {'J', 'B'}, {'M', 'X'}, {'M', 'V'}, {'M', 'J'}, {'X', 'J'}, {'M', 'X', 'B'}, {'M', 'V', 'B'}, {'M', 'J', 'B'}, {'X', 'V', 'B'}, {'X', 'J', 'B'}, {'J', 'V', 'B'}, {'M', 'X', 'V'}, {'M', 'X', 'J'}, {'M', 'J', 'V'}, {'M', 'X', 'V', 'B'}, {'M', 'X', 'J', 'B'}, {'M', 'J', 'V', 'B'}, {'X', 'V', 'J', 'B'}, {'M', 'X', 'V', 'J'}, {'B', 'M', 'V', 'J', 'X'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, M, B, X, N, V, J and directed edges G->X, G->V, B->V, N->J, M->N, M->B, G->N, G->M, B->X, M->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "14558094", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path G->V<-B<-M->N.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, M, B, X, N, V, J and directed edges G->X, G->V, B->V, N->J, M->N, M->B, G->N, G->M, B->X, M->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "14558094", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path M->N<-G->X<-B be blocked by nodeset {'X', 'J', 'N'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, M, B, X, N, V, J and directed edges G->X, G->V, B->V, N->J, M->N, M->B, G->N, G->M, B->X, M->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "14558094", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path B<-M<-G->V?\nA. {'X'}\nB. {'N'}\nC. {'M', 'X', 'G'}\nD. {'J'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, J, M, Y, F, V, C, G and directed edges C->G, F->V, J->C, W->J, W->G, J->Y, J->F, W->V, J->V, W->Y, M->C, M->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "86225333", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path W->V<-J->C.", "answer": "[set(), {'G'}, {'M'}, {'J'}, {'F'}, {'Y'}, {'M', 'G'}, {'J', 'G'}, {'G', 'F'}, {'G', 'Y'}, {'M', 'J'}, {'M', 'F'}, {'M', 'Y'}, {'J', 'V'}, {'J', 'F'}, {'J', 'Y'}, {'F', 'Y'}, {'M', 'J', 'G'}, {'M', 'G', 'F'}, {'M', 'G', 'Y'}, {'V', 'G', 'J'}, {'J', 'G', 'F'}, {'J', 'G', 'Y'}, {'G', 'F', 'Y'}, {'M', 'J', 'V'}, {'M', 'J', 'F'}, {'M', 'J', 'Y'}, {'M', 'F', 'Y'}, {'J', 'V', 'F'}, {'J', 'V', 'Y'}, {'J', 'F', 'Y'}, {'M', 'V', 'G', 'J'}, {'M', 'J', 'G', 'F'}, {'M', 'J', 'G', 'Y'}, {'M', 'G', 'F', 'Y'}, {'V', 'G', 'F', 'J'}, {'V', 'G', 'J', 'Y'}, {'J', 'G', 'F', 'Y'}, {'M', 'J', 'V', 'F'}, {'M', 'J', 'V', 'Y'}, {'M', 'J', 'F', 'Y'}, {'J', 'V', 'F', 'Y'}, {'G', 'M', 'V', 'J', 'F'}, {'G', 'M', 'V', 'J', 'Y'}, {'G', 'M', 'J', 'F', 'Y'}, {'G', 'V', 'J', 'F', 'Y'}, {'M', 'V', 'J', 'F', 'Y'}, {'G', 'M', 'V', 'J', 'F', 'Y'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, J, M, Y, F, V, C, G and directed edges C->G, F->V, J->C, W->J, W->G, J->Y, J->F, W->V, J->V, W->Y, M->C, M->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "86225333", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path W->V<-J->C.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, J, M, Y, F, V, C, G and directed edges C->G, F->V, J->C, W->J, W->G, J->Y, J->F, W->V, J->V, W->Y, M->C, M->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "86225333", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path W->V<-F<-J->C->G be blocked by nodeset {'V', 'Y'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes W, J, M, Y, F, V, C, G and directed edges C->G, F->V, J->C, W->J, W->G, J->Y, J->F, W->V, J->V, W->Y, M->C, M->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "86225333", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path J->V<-W->Y?\nA. {'V', 'F', 'W'}\nB. {'M', 'V', 'G', 'F'}\nC. {'V', 'G', 'F', 'C'}\nD. {'M', 'V', 'C'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, U, A, Z, Y, D, C, I and directed edges U->I, A->Z, K->A, C->I, A->D, A->I, Z->I, K->Y, Y->C.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "13080398", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path Y->C->I.", "answer": "[{'C'}, {'D', 'C'}, {'Z', 'C'}, {'C', 'A'}, {'C', 'K'}, {'C', 'U'}, {'D', 'Z', 'C'}, {'D', 'C', 'A'}, {'D', 'C', 'K'}, {'D', 'C', 'U'}, {'Z', 'C', 'A'}, {'Z', 'C', 'K'}, {'Z', 'C', 'U'}, {'C', 'A', 'K'}, {'C', 'A', 'U'}, {'C', 'U', 'K'}, {'D', 'Z', 'C', 'A'}, {'D', 'Z', 'C', 'K'}, {'D', 'Z', 'C', 'U'}, {'D', 'C', 'A', 'K'}, {'D', 'C', 'A', 'U'}, {'D', 'C', 'U', 'K'}, {'Z', 'C', 'A', 'K'}, {'Z', 'C', 'A', 'U'}, {'Z', 'C', 'U', 'K'}, {'C', 'A', 'U', 'K'}, {'D', 'Z', 'A', 'K', 'C'}, {'D', 'Z', 'A', 'U', 'C'}, {'D', 'Z', 'U', 'K', 'C'}, {'D', 'A', 'U', 'K', 'C'}, {'Z', 'A', 'U', 'K', 'C'}, {'D', 'Z', 'A', 'U', 'K', 'C'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, U, A, Z, Y, D, C, I and directed edges U->I, A->Z, K->A, C->I, A->D, A->I, Z->I, K->Y, Y->C.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "13080398", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path Y->C->I.", "answer": "{'C'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, U, A, Z, Y, D, C, I and directed edges U->I, A->Z, K->A, C->I, A->D, A->I, Z->I, K->Y, Y->C.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "13080398", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path A<-K->Y->C->I<-Z be blocked by nodeset {'D', 'I', 'C', 'K'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, U, A, Z, Y, D, C, I and directed edges U->I, A->Z, K->A, C->I, A->D, A->I, Z->I, K->Y, Y->C.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "13080398", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path Y<-K->A->Z->I<-C?\nA. {'D', 'I'}\nB. {'I', 'A', 'K'}\nC. {'I', 'U'}\nD. {'I'}", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, X, H, K, D, B, S, U and directed edges D->B, D->S, H->K, X->S, H->D, S->U, X->U, N->K, K->B, H->B, D->U, H->U.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "72525447", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path H->B<-D->S<-X->U.", "answer": "[set(), {'D'}, {'S'}, {'N'}, {'B'}, {'K'}, {'X'}, {'D', 'S'}, {'D', 'N'}, {'D', 'B'}, {'D', 'K'}, {'X', 'D'}, {'S', 'N'}, {'S', 'K'}, {'X', 'S'}, {'N', 'B'}, {'N', 'K'}, {'X', 'N'}, {'B', 'K'}, {'X', 'B'}, {'X', 'K'}, {'D', 'S', 'N'}, {'D', 'S', 'B'}, {'D', 'S', 'K'}, {'X', 'D', 'S'}, {'D', 'N', 'B'}, {'D', 'N', 'K'}, {'X', 'D', 'N'}, {'D', 'B', 'K'}, {'X', 'D', 'B'}, {'X', 'D', 'K'}, {'S', 'N', 'K'}, {'X', 'S', 'N'}, {'X', 'S', 'B'}, {'X', 'S', 'K'}, {'N', 'B', 'K'}, {'X', 'N', 'B'}, {'X', 'N', 'K'}, {'X', 'B', 'K'}, {'D', 'S', 'N', 'B'}, {'D', 'S', 'N', 'K'}, {'X', 'D', 'S', 'N'}, {'D', 'S', 'B', 'K'}, {'X', 'D', 'S', 'B'}, {'X', 'D', 'S', 'K'}, {'D', 'N', 'B', 'K'}, {'X', 'D', 'N', 'B'}, {'X', 'D', 'N', 'K'}, {'X', 'D', 'B', 'K'}, {'X', 'S', 'N', 'B'}, {'X', 'S', 'N', 'K'}, {'X', 'S', 'B', 'K'}, {'X', 'N', 'B', 'K'}, {'D', 'S', 'N', 'B', 'K'}, {'D', 'S', 'N', 'B', 'X'}, {'D', 'S', 'N', 'K', 'X'}, {'D', 'S', 'B', 'K', 'X'}, {'D', 'N', 'B', 'K', 'X'}, {'S', 'N', 'B', 'K', 'X'}, {'D', 'S', 'N', 'B', 'K', 'X'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, X, H, K, D, B, S, U and directed edges D->B, D->S, H->K, X->S, H->D, S->U, X->U, N->K, K->B, H->B, D->U, H->U.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "72525447", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path H->B<-D->S<-X->U.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, X, H, K, D, B, S, U and directed edges D->B, D->S, H->K, X->S, H->D, S->U, X->U, N->K, K->B, H->B, D->U, H->U.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "72525447", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path D->S->U be blocked by nodeset {'S', 'N', 'K'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, X, H, K, D, B, S, U and directed edges D->B, D->S, H->K, X->S, H->D, S->U, X->U, N->K, K->B, H->B, D->U, H->U.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "72525447", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path H->K->B<-D->U?\nA. {'X', 'D'}\nB. {'S', 'N', 'B'}\nC. {'X', 'B'}\nD. {'X', 'N', 'B'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Y, U, A, K, M, V, Z, B, P and directed edges M->Z, Y->A, A->K, A->P, K->V, U->V, A->V, Z->B, Y->P, U->M, U->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "11585581", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path Y->A->V.", "answer": "[{'A'}, {'Z', 'A'}, {'A', 'B'}, {'A', 'K'}, {'M', 'A'}, {'A', 'U'}, {'P', 'A'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B'}, {'Z', 'A', 'K'}, {'M', 'Z', 'A'}, {'Z', 'A', 'U'}, {'P', 'Z', 'A'}, {'A', 'B', 'K'}, {'M', 'A', 'B'}, {'A', 'B', 'U'}, {'P', 'A', 'B'}, {'M', 'A', 'K'}, {'A', 'U', 'K'}, {'P', 'A', 'K'}, {'M', 'A', 'U'}, {'M', 'P', 'A'}, {'P', 'A', 'U'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'K'}, {'M', 'Z', 'A', 'B'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'U'}, {'P', 'Z', 'A', 'B'}, {'M', 'Z', 'A', 'K'}, {'Z', 'A', 'U', 'K'}, {'P', 'Z', 'A', 'K'}, {'M', 'Z', 'A', 'U'}, {'M', 'Z', 'A', 'P'}, {'P', 'Z', 'A', 'U'}, {'M', 'A', 'B', 'K'}, {'U', 'A', 'B', 'K'}, {'P', 'A', 'B', 'K'}, {'M', 'A', 'B', 'U'}, {'M', 'P', 'A', 'B'}, {'P', 'A', 'B', 'U'}, {'M', 'A', 'U', 'K'}, {'M', 'P', 'A', 'K'}, {'P', 'A', 'U', 'K'}, {'M', 'P', 'A', 'U'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'K', 'M'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'U', 'K'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'K', 'P'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'U', 'M'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'M', 'P'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'U', 'P'}, {'Z', 'A', 'U', 'M', 'K'}, {'Z', 'A', 'K', 'M', 'P'}, {'Z', 'A', 'U', 'K', 'P'}, {'Z', 'A', 'U', 'M', 'P'}, {'A', 'B', 'U', 'M', 'K'}, {'A', 'B', 'K', 'M', 'P'}, {'A', 'B', 'U', 'K', 'P'}, {'A', 'B', 'U', 'M', 'P'}, {'A', 'U', 'M', 'K', 'P'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'K', 'M', 'U'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'K', 'M', 'P'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'U', 'K', 'P'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'U', 'M', 'P'}, {'Z', 'A', 'U', 'M', 'K', 'P'}, {'A', 'B', 'U', 'M', 'K', 'P'}, {'Z', 'A', 'B', 'K', 'M', 'U', 'P'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Y, U, A, K, M, V, Z, B, P and directed edges M->Z, Y->A, A->K, A->P, K->V, U->V, A->V, Z->B, Y->P, U->M, U->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "11585581", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path Y->A->V.", "answer": "{'A'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Y, U, A, K, M, V, Z, B, P and directed edges M->Z, Y->A, A->K, A->P, K->V, U->V, A->V, Z->B, Y->P, U->M, U->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "11585581", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path M->Z->B be blocked by nodeset {'Z', 'A', 'U', 'P', 'Y'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Y, U, A, K, M, V, Z, B, P and directed edges M->Z, Y->A, A->K, A->P, K->V, U->V, A->V, Z->B, Y->P, U->M, U->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "11585581", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path Y->P<-A->V<-K?\nA. {'Z', 'B', 'M', 'P', 'V'}\nB. {'P', 'V', 'Z', 'U'}\nC. {'Z', 'B', 'U', 'P', 'V'}\nD. {'V', 'Z', 'B', 'U'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, E, Z, I, V, Q, T, D, R and directed edges M->E, I->D, V->D, Q->T, T->R, M->I, M->V, Z->I, E->D, E->R, E->Q, Z->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "67443221", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path M->V->D<-I<-Z->Q<-E.", "answer": "[set(), {'D'}, {'I'}, {'Z'}, {'V'}, {'Q'}, {'T'}, {'R'}, {'D', 'I'}, {'D', 'Z'}, {'D', 'V'}, {'I', 'Z'}, {'V', 'I'}, {'I', 'Q'}, {'I', 'T'}, {'I', 'R'}, {'V', 'Z'}, {'Z', 'Q'}, {'Z', 'T'}, {'Z', 'R'}, {'V', 'Q'}, {'V', 'T'}, {'V', 'R'}, {'T', 'Q'}, {'R', 'Q'}, {'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z'}, {'D', 'I', 'V'}, {'D', 'I', 'Q'}, {'D', 'I', 'T'}, {'D', 'I', 'R'}, {'D', 'V', 'Z'}, {'D', 'Z', 'Q'}, {'D', 'Z', 'T'}, {'D', 'Z', 'R'}, {'D', 'V', 'Q'}, {'D', 'V', 'T'}, {'D', 'V', 'R'}, {'V', 'I', 'Z'}, {'I', 'Z', 'Q'}, {'I', 'Z', 'T'}, {'I', 'Z', 'R'}, {'V', 'I', 'Q'}, {'V', 'I', 'T'}, {'V', 'I', 'R'}, {'I', 'T', 'Q'}, {'I', 'R', 'Q'}, {'I', 'T', 'R'}, {'V', 'Z', 'Q'}, {'V', 'Z', 'T'}, {'V', 'Z', 'R'}, {'Z', 'T', 'Q'}, {'Z', 'R', 'Q'}, {'Z', 'T', 'R'}, {'V', 'T', 'Q'}, {'V', 'R', 'Q'}, {'V', 'T', 'R'}, {'T', 'R', 'Q'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'V'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'Q'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'T'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'V', 'Q'}, {'D', 'I', 'T', 'V'}, {'D', 'I', 'V', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'T', 'Q'}, {'D', 'I', 'R', 'Q'}, {'D', 'I', 'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'V', 'Z', 'Q'}, {'D', 'V', 'Z', 'T'}, {'D', 'V', 'Z', 'R'}, {'D', 'Z', 'T', 'Q'}, {'D', 'Z', 'R', 'Q'}, {'D', 'Z', 'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'V', 'T', 'Q'}, {'D', 'V', 'R', 'Q'}, {'D', 'V', 'T', 'R'}, {'V', 'I', 'Z', 'Q'}, {'V', 'I', 'Z', 'T'}, {'V', 'I', 'Z', 'R'}, {'I', 'Z', 'T', 'Q'}, {'I', 'Z', 'R', 'Q'}, {'I', 'Z', 'T', 'R'}, {'V', 'I', 'T', 'Q'}, {'V', 'I', 'R', 'Q'}, {'V', 'I', 'T', 'R'}, {'I', 'T', 'R', 'Q'}, {'V', 'Z', 'T', 'Q'}, {'V', 'Z', 'R', 'Q'}, {'V', 'Z', 'T', 'R'}, {'R', 'Z', 'T', 'Q'}, {'V', 'T', 'R', 'Q'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'V', 'Q'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'V', 'T'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'V', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'Q', 'T'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'Q', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'V', 'Q', 'T'}, {'D', 'I', 'V', 'Q', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'V', 'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'Q', 'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'Z', 'V', 'Q', 'T'}, {'D', 'Z', 'V', 'Q', 'R'}, {'D', 'Z', 'V', 'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'Z', 'Q', 'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'V', 'Q', 'T', 'R'}, {'I', 'Z', 'V', 'Q', 'T'}, {'I', 'Z', 'V', 'Q', 'R'}, {'I', 'Z', 'V', 'T', 'R'}, {'I', 'Z', 'Q', 'T', 'R'}, {'I', 'V', 'Q', 'T', 'R'}, {'Z', 'V', 'Q', 'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'V', 'Q', 'T'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'V', 'Q', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'V', 'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'Q', 'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'V', 'Q', 'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'Z', 'V', 'Q', 'T', 'R'}, {'I', 'Z', 'V', 'Q', 'T', 'R'}, {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'V', 'Q', 'T', 'R'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, E, Z, I, V, Q, T, D, R and directed edges M->E, I->D, V->D, Q->T, T->R, M->I, M->V, Z->I, E->D, E->R, E->Q, Z->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "67443221", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path M->V->D<-I<-Z->Q<-E.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, E, Z, I, V, Q, T, D, R and directed edges M->E, I->D, V->D, Q->T, T->R, M->I, M->V, Z->I, E->D, E->R, E->Q, Z->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "67443221", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path Z->Q->T->R<-E<-M->I be blocked by nodeset {'D', 'T', 'Q'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, E, Z, I, V, Q, T, D, R and directed edges M->E, I->D, V->D, Q->T, T->R, M->I, M->V, Z->I, E->D, E->R, E->Q, Z->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "67443221", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path M->E->R<-T?\nA. {'Z', 'R'}\nB. {'D', 'I', 'Z', 'V', 'R'}\nC. {'D', 'Z', 'R', 'Q'}\nD. {'Z', 'Q'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, K, M, F, J, C, R, Z, A and directed edges J->C, C->Z, F->J, C->R, M->Z, J->Z, K->M, G->M, F->A, F->R, G->C, K->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "63905178", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path G->C->Z.", "answer": "[{'C'}, {'C', 'A'}, {'C', 'K'}, {'M', 'C'}, {'J', 'C'}, {'F', 'C'}, {'C', 'R'}, {'C', 'A', 'K'}, {'M', 'C', 'A'}, {'J', 'C', 'A'}, {'F', 'C', 'A'}, {'C', 'A', 'R'}, {'M', 'C', 'K'}, {'J', 'C', 'K'}, {'F', 'C', 'K'}, {'C', 'R', 'K'}, {'M', 'J', 'C'}, {'M', 'F', 'C'}, {'M', 'C', 'R'}, {'J', 'F', 'C'}, {'J', 'C', 'R'}, {'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'M', 'C', 'A', 'K'}, {'J', 'C', 'A', 'K'}, {'F', 'C', 'A', 'K'}, {'C', 'A', 'R', 'K'}, {'M', 'J', 'C', 'A'}, {'M', 'F', 'C', 'A'}, {'M', 'C', 'A', 'R'}, {'J', 'F', 'C', 'A'}, {'J', 'C', 'A', 'R'}, {'F', 'C', 'A', 'R'}, {'M', 'J', 'C', 'K'}, {'M', 'F', 'C', 'K'}, {'M', 'C', 'R', 'K'}, {'J', 'F', 'C', 'K'}, {'J', 'C', 'R', 'K'}, {'F', 'C', 'R', 'K'}, {'M', 'J', 'F', 'C'}, {'M', 'J', 'C', 'R'}, {'M', 'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'J', 'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'A', 'K', 'M', 'J', 'C'}, {'A', 'K', 'M', 'F', 'C'}, {'A', 'K', 'M', 'C', 'R'}, {'A', 'K', 'J', 'F', 'C'}, {'A', 'K', 'J', 'C', 'R'}, {'A', 'K', 'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'A', 'M', 'J', 'F', 'C'}, {'A', 'M', 'J', 'C', 'R'}, {'A', 'M', 'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'A', 'J', 'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'K', 'M', 'J', 'F', 'C'}, {'K', 'M', 'J', 'C', 'R'}, {'K', 'M', 'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'K', 'J', 'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'M', 'J', 'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'A', 'K', 'M', 'J', 'F', 'C'}, {'A', 'K', 'M', 'J', 'C', 'R'}, {'A', 'K', 'M', 'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'A', 'K', 'J', 'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'A', 'M', 'J', 'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'K', 'M', 'J', 'F', 'C', 'R'}, {'A', 'K', 'M', 'J', 'F', 'C', 'R'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, K, M, F, J, C, R, Z, A and directed edges J->C, C->Z, F->J, C->R, M->Z, J->Z, K->M, G->M, F->A, F->R, G->C, K->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "63905178", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path G->C->Z.", "answer": "{'C'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, K, M, F, J, C, R, Z, A and directed edges J->C, C->Z, F->J, C->R, M->Z, J->Z, K->M, G->M, F->A, F->R, G->C, K->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "63905178", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path G->C->R<-F->J->Z<-M be blocked by nodeset {'Z', 'R', 'K'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, K, M, F, J, C, R, Z, A and directed edges J->C, C->Z, F->J, C->R, M->Z, J->Z, K->M, G->M, F->A, F->R, G->C, K->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "63905178", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path K->M<-G->C->Z<-J<-F->R?\nA. {'J', 'Z', 'A'}\nB. {'M', 'Z', 'A'}\nC. {'Z'}\nD. {'Z', 'A'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes F, J, T, P, directed edges T->P, J->T, F->P, F->T, F->J, J->P and bi-directed edges F<->P.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "80821416", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path F->P<-T<-J.", "answer": "[set(), {'T'}, {'P', 'T'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes F, J, T, P, directed edges T->P, J->T, F->P, F->T, F->J, J->P and bi-directed edges F<->P.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "80821416", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path F->P<-T<-J.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes F, J, T, P, directed edges T->P, J->T, F->P, F->T, F->J, J->P and bi-directed edges F<->P.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "80821416", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path F<->P<-J->T be blocked by nodeset set()?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes F, J, T, P, directed edges T->P, J->T, F->P, F->T, F->J, J->P and bi-directed edges F<->P.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "80821416", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path F->T<-J?\nA. {'P', 'T'}\nB. {'P'}\nC. set()\nD. {'T'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, M, W, B, directed edges K->B, K->W, W->B, M->W, K->M and bi-directed edges M<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "22786568", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path M->W<-K->B.", "answer": "[set(), {'K'}, {'W', 'K'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, M, W, B, directed edges K->B, K->W, W->B, M->W, K->M and bi-directed edges M<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "22786568", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path M->W<-K->B.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, M, W, B, directed edges K->B, K->W, W->B, M->W, K->M and bi-directed edges M<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "22786568", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path M<->W->B be blocked by nodeset {'K'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, M, W, B, directed edges K->B, K->W, W->B, M->W, K->M and bi-directed edges M<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "22786568", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path K->M<->W?\nA. set()\nB. {'M', 'B'}\nC. {'B'}\nD. {'M'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, J, D, H, directed edges P->J, D->H, J->H, P->H, J->D and bi-directed edges D<->H, P<->J, P<->H.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "26680650", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path P<->H<-D<-J.", "answer": "[set(), {'D'}, {'D', 'H'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, J, D, H, directed edges P->J, D->H, J->H, P->H, J->D and bi-directed edges D<->H, P<->J, P<->H.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "26680650", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path P<->H<-D<-J.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, J, D, H, directed edges P->J, D->H, J->H, P->H, J->D and bi-directed edges D<->H, P<->J, P<->H.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "26680650", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path P->J->D->H be blocked by nodeset set()?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, J, D, H, directed edges P->J, D->H, J->H, P->H, J->D and bi-directed edges D<->H, P<->J, P<->H.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "26680650", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path J<->P<->H?\nA. {'P', 'D'}\nB. {'D'}\nC. {'P'}\nD. set()", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes V, O, R, X, N, directed edges O->R, X->N, R->N, V->X, O->N, V->O, R->X, V->R, O->X and bi-directed edges O<->N, V<->X, V<->R, R<->X, R<->N.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "87587820", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path V<->X->N<->O->R.", "answer": "[set(), {'X'}, {'O'}, {'X', 'N'}, {'X', 'O'}, {'N', 'O'}, {'X', 'N', 'O'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes V, O, R, X, N, directed edges O->R, X->N, R->N, V->X, O->N, V->O, R->X, V->R, O->X and bi-directed edges O<->N, V<->X, V<->R, R<->X, R<->N.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "87587820", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path V<->X->N<->O->R.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes V, O, R, X, N, directed edges O->R, X->N, R->N, V->X, O->N, V->O, R->X, V->R, O->X and bi-directed edges O<->N, V<->X, V<->R, R<->X, R<->N.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "87587820", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path V<->X->N<->R be blocked by nodeset {'N'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes V, O, R, X, N, directed edges O->R, X->N, R->N, V->X, O->N, V->O, R->X, V->R, O->X and bi-directed edges O<->N, V<->X, V<->R, R<->X, R<->N.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "87587820", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path V->O<->N?\nA. {'O', 'R'}\nB. set()\nC. {'R'}\nD. {'X', 'O'}", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, B, U, C, M, directed edges B->U, K->U, K->B, C->M, B->C, U->M, U->C, K->C and bi-directed edges B<->M, K<->U, U<->M, C<->M.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "31345404", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path K->U<-B->C->M.", "answer": "[set(), {'C'}, {'B'}, {'C', 'B'}, {'C', 'U'}, {'B', 'U'}, {'C', 'B', 'U'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, B, U, C, M, directed edges B->U, K->U, K->B, C->M, B->C, U->M, U->C, K->C and bi-directed edges B<->M, K<->U, U<->M, C<->M.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "31345404", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path K->U<-B->C->M.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, B, U, C, M, directed edges B->U, K->U, K->B, C->M, B->C, U->M, U->C, K->C and bi-directed edges B<->M, K<->U, U<->M, C<->M.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "31345404", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path B<-K<->U->M be blocked by nodeset {'C'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, B, U, C, M, directed edges B->U, K->U, K->B, C->M, B->C, U->M, U->C, K->C and bi-directed edges B<->M, K<->U, U<->M, C<->M.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "31345404", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path B->C<->M?\nA. {'C', 'U'}\nB. {'C', 'K'}\nC. {'C'}\nD. {'U', 'K'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes M, T, Z, G, N, directed edges G->N, Z->G, T->G, M->Z, Z->N and bi-directed edges T<->G, Z<->N, M<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "76337240", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path G<-T<->M->Z->N.", "answer": "[{'M'}, {'Z'}, {'T'}, {'M', 'Z'}, {'M', 'T'}, {'Z', 'T'}, {'M', 'Z', 'T'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes M, T, Z, G, N, directed edges G->N, Z->G, T->G, M->Z, Z->N and bi-directed edges T<->G, Z<->N, M<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "76337240", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path G<-T<->M->Z->N.", "answer": "{'M'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes M, T, Z, G, N, directed edges G->N, Z->G, T->G, M->Z, Z->N and bi-directed edges T<->G, Z<->N, M<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "76337240", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path M->Z<->N<-G be blocked by nodeset set()?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes M, T, Z, G, N, directed edges G->N, Z->G, T->G, M->Z, Z->N and bi-directed edges T<->G, Z<->N, M<->T.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "76337240", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path Z->N<-G?\nA. {'M', 'T', 'N'}\nB. {'N'}\nC. set()\nD. {'T', 'N'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes G, E, J, F, M, Y, directed edges J->M, E->J, G->J, F->Y, E->Y, M->Y, J->Y, G->F, J->F, G->M and bi-directed edges G<->E, G<->Y, G<->F, J<->Y, E<->J, E<->M, M<->Y.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "53721553", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path E<->M<-J<-G<->Y.", "answer": "[set(), {'J'}, {'G'}, {'F'}, {'M', 'J'}, {'M', 'G'}, {'J', 'G'}, {'J', 'F'}, {'G', 'F'}, {'M', 'J', 'G'}, {'M', 'J', 'F'}, {'M', 'G', 'F'}, {'J', 'G', 'F'}, {'M', 'J', 'G', 'F'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes G, E, J, F, M, Y, directed edges J->M, E->J, G->J, F->Y, E->Y, M->Y, J->Y, G->F, J->F, G->M and bi-directed edges G<->E, G<->Y, G<->F, J<->Y, E<->J, E<->M, M<->Y.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "53721553", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path E<->M<-J<-G<->Y.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes G, E, J, F, M, Y, directed edges J->M, E->J, G->J, F->Y, E->Y, M->Y, J->Y, G->F, J->F, G->M and bi-directed edges G<->E, G<->Y, G<->F, J<->Y, E<->J, E<->M, M<->Y.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "53721553", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path J<-E<->M<-G->F->Y be blocked by nodeset {'G'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes G, E, J, F, M, Y, directed edges J->M, E->J, G->J, F->Y, E->Y, M->Y, J->Y, G->F, J->F, G->M and bi-directed edges G<->E, G<->Y, G<->F, J<->Y, E<->J, E<->M, M<->Y.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "53721553", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path J<-E->Y<->G<->F?\nA. {'M', 'G', 'E', 'Y'}\nB. {'Y'}\nC. {'M', 'Y'}\nD. {'G', 'Y'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes W, D, X, M, K, P, directed edges W->P, W->M, X->M, D->P, D->X, X->K, W->D, D->K, D->M, M->P and bi-directed edges W<->P, D<->X, X<->K.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "53759464", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path X->K<-D->P<-M.", "answer": "[set(), {'P'}, {'D'}, {'W'}, {'K'}, {'P', 'D'}, {'P', 'W'}, {'D', 'W'}, {'D', 'K'}, {'W', 'K'}, {'P', 'D', 'W'}, {'P', 'D', 'K'}, {'D', 'W', 'K'}, {'P', 'D', 'W', 'K'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes W, D, X, M, K, P, directed edges W->P, W->M, X->M, D->P, D->X, X->K, W->D, D->K, D->M, M->P and bi-directed edges W<->P, D<->X, X<->K.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "53759464", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path X->K<-D->P<-M.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes W, D, X, M, K, P, directed edges W->P, W->M, X->M, D->P, D->X, X->K, W->D, D->K, D->M, M->P and bi-directed edges W<->P, D<->X, X<->K.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "53759464", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path W<->P<-D->K<-X->M be blocked by nodeset {'P', 'D', 'K'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes W, D, X, M, K, P, directed edges W->P, W->M, X->M, D->P, D->X, X->K, W->D, D->K, D->M, M->P and bi-directed edges W<->P, D<->X, X<->K.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "53759464", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path X<-D->M->P?\nA. {'W'}\nB. {'K'}\nC. set()\nD. {'D', 'W'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, V, S, O, T, Z, directed edges V->T, V->S, Y->S, Y->Z, T->Z, O->T and bi-directed edges Y<->S, T<->Z, S<->Z.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13376836", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path O->T<-V->S<->Z.", "answer": "[set(), {'V'}, {'T'}, {'S'}, {'Y'}, {'V', 'T'}, {'V', 'S'}, {'V', 'Y'}, {'T', 'Y'}, {'S', 'Y'}, {'V', 'T', 'S'}, {'V', 'T', 'Y'}, {'V', 'S', 'Y'}, {'V', 'T', 'S', 'Y'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, V, S, O, T, Z, directed edges V->T, V->S, Y->S, Y->Z, T->Z, O->T and bi-directed edges Y<->S, T<->Z, S<->Z.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13376836", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path O->T<-V->S<->Z.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, V, S, O, T, Z, directed edges V->T, V->S, Y->S, Y->Z, T->Z, O->T and bi-directed edges Y<->S, T<->Z, S<->Z.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13376836", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path Y->Z<->T<-V->S be blocked by nodeset {'Z', 'T', 'O'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, V, S, O, T, Z, directed edges V->T, V->S, Y->S, Y->Z, T->Z, O->T and bi-directed edges Y<->S, T<->Z, S<->Z.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13376836", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path V->S<->Z?\nA. {'T', 'S', 'O', 'Y'}\nB. {'S', 'O'}\nC. {'T', 'S'}\nD. {'T'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes W, J, G, U, E, N, V, directed edges N->V, J->N, U->E, J->G, G->U, G->N, W->E, W->V, W->G and bi-directed edges W<->E, E<->V, U<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "27725846", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path W->V<->E.", "answer": "[set(), {'G'}, {'N'}, {'U'}, {'J'}, {'G', 'N'}, {'G', 'U'}, {'J', 'G'}, {'N', 'U'}, {'J', 'N'}, {'J', 'U'}, {'G', 'N', 'U'}, {'J', 'G', 'N'}, {'J', 'G', 'U'}, {'J', 'N', 'U'}, {'J', 'G', 'N', 'U'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes W, J, G, U, E, N, V, directed edges N->V, J->N, U->E, J->G, G->U, G->N, W->E, W->V, W->G and bi-directed edges W<->E, E<->V, U<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "27725846", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path W->V<->E.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes W, J, G, U, E, N, V, directed edges N->V, J->N, U->E, J->G, G->U, G->N, W->E, W->V, W->G and bi-directed edges W<->E, E<->V, U<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "27725846", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path G<-W->E<->V<-N be blocked by nodeset {'J', 'V', 'E', 'U'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes W, J, G, U, E, N, V, directed edges N->V, J->N, U->E, J->G, G->U, G->N, W->E, W->V, W->G and bi-directed edges W<->E, E<->V, U<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "27725846", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path W->G<-J->N->V<->E?\nA. {'V', 'U'}\nB. {'V', 'G', 'U'}\nC. {'J', 'V', 'N'}\nD. {'V'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, B, X, L, V, U, D, directed edges Q->D, B->X, X->V, Q->X, B->V, Q->L, X->U, V->U, Q->V and bi-directed edges X<->U, B<->L, B<->V, Q<->L, B<->U.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "40163509", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path X->U<->B<->L<->Q->V.", "answer": "[set(), {'D'}, {'B'}, {'U'}, {'Q'}, {'L'}, {'D', 'B'}, {'D', 'U'}, {'D', 'Q'}, {'D', 'L'}, {'B', 'U'}, {'Q', 'B'}, {'L', 'B'}, {'Q', 'U'}, {'L', 'Q'}, {'D', 'B', 'U'}, {'D', 'Q', 'B'}, {'D', 'L', 'B'}, {'D', 'Q', 'U'}, {'D', 'L', 'Q'}, {'Q', 'B', 'U'}, {'L', 'Q', 'B'}, {'L', 'Q', 'U'}, {'D', 'Q', 'B', 'U'}, {'D', 'L', 'Q', 'B'}, {'D', 'L', 'Q', 'U'}, {'L', 'Q', 'B', 'U'}, {'D', 'B', 'U', 'Q', 'L'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, B, X, L, V, U, D, directed edges Q->D, B->X, X->V, Q->X, B->V, Q->L, X->U, V->U, Q->V and bi-directed edges X<->U, B<->L, B<->V, Q<->L, B<->U.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "40163509", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path X->U<->B<->L<->Q->V.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, B, X, L, V, U, D, directed edges Q->D, B->X, X->V, Q->X, B->V, Q->L, X->U, V->U, Q->V and bi-directed edges X<->U, B<->L, B<->V, Q<->L, B<->U.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "40163509", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path B<->L<-Q->X->U<-V be blocked by nodeset {'L', 'U'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, B, X, L, V, U, D, directed edges Q->D, B->X, X->V, Q->X, B->V, Q->L, X->U, V->U, Q->V and bi-directed edges X<->U, B<->L, B<->V, Q<->L, B<->U.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "40163509", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path B<->V<-Q->X?\nA. {'D', 'V', 'L', 'U'}\nB. {'U'}\nC. {'D', 'U'}\nD. {'D', 'Q', 'U'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes S, B, H, J, V, F, Y, directed edges J->Y, H->V, B->H, J->V, F->Y, S->H, S->V and bi-directed edges B<->F, H<->V.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "10524701", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path S->V<-H.", "answer": "[set(), {'B'}, {'J'}, {'F'}, {'Y'}, {'J', 'B'}, {'F', 'B'}, {'B', 'Y'}, {'J', 'F'}, {'J', 'Y'}, {'F', 'Y'}, {'J', 'F', 'B'}, {'J', 'B', 'Y'}, {'F', 'B', 'Y'}, {'J', 'F', 'Y'}, {'J', 'F', 'B', 'Y'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes S, B, H, J, V, F, Y, directed edges J->Y, H->V, B->H, J->V, F->Y, S->H, S->V and bi-directed edges B<->F, H<->V.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "10524701", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path S->V<-H.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes S, B, H, J, V, F, Y, directed edges J->Y, H->V, B->H, J->V, F->Y, S->H, S->V and bi-directed edges B<->F, H<->V.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "10524701", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path J->V<->H<-B<->F->Y be blocked by nodeset {'V', 'H'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes S, B, H, J, V, F, Y, directed edges J->Y, H->V, B->H, J->V, F->Y, S->H, S->V and bi-directed edges B<->F, H<->V.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "10524701", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path S->H->V?\nA. {'H', 'B'}\nB. {'J', 'B'}\nC. {'J', 'F', 'Y'}\nD. {'F', 'Y'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, P, Q, D, J, V, K, W, directed edges P->Q, P->J, D->V, Q->K, B->P, B->W, B->K, J->V, V->K, J->K and bi-directed edges P<->W, K<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "99284596", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path J->K<-V.", "answer": "[set(), {'D'}, {'B'}, {'W'}, {'P'}, {'Q'}, {'D', 'B'}, {'D', 'W'}, {'P', 'D'}, {'D', 'Q'}, {'W', 'B'}, {'P', 'B'}, {'Q', 'B'}, {'P', 'W'}, {'W', 'Q'}, {'P', 'Q'}, {'D', 'W', 'B'}, {'P', 'D', 'B'}, {'D', 'Q', 'B'}, {'P', 'D', 'W'}, {'D', 'W', 'Q'}, {'P', 'D', 'Q'}, {'P', 'W', 'B'}, {'Q', 'W', 'B'}, {'P', 'Q', 'B'}, {'P', 'W', 'Q'}, {'P', 'D', 'W', 'B'}, {'D', 'Q', 'W', 'B'}, {'P', 'D', 'Q', 'B'}, {'P', 'D', 'W', 'Q'}, {'P', 'Q', 'W', 'B'}, {'D', 'B', 'W', 'P', 'Q'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, P, Q, D, J, V, K, W, directed edges P->Q, P->J, D->V, Q->K, B->P, B->W, B->K, J->V, V->K, J->K and bi-directed edges P<->W, K<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "99284596", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path J->K<-V.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, P, Q, D, J, V, K, W, directed edges P->Q, P->J, D->V, Q->K, B->P, B->W, B->K, J->V, V->K, J->K and bi-directed edges P<->W, K<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "99284596", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path D->V<-J->K be blocked by nodeset {'B', 'W', 'P', 'V', 'Q'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, P, Q, D, J, V, K, W, directed edges P->Q, P->J, D->V, Q->K, B->P, B->W, B->K, J->V, V->K, J->K and bi-directed edges P<->W, K<->W.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "99284596", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path P<->W<->K<-Q?\nA. {'V', 'W', 'K'}\nB. {'W', 'B', 'K'}\nC. {'D', 'V', 'K'}\nD. {'V', 'W', 'B', 'K'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes J, H, O, F, Q, U, K, I, directed edges F->K, J->F, O->F, K->I, O->U, H->O, J->K, J->U, J->Q and bi-directed edges F<->I, H<->K, F<->Q, J<->U, H<->F.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13672825", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path K<-J<->U<-O<-H<->F<->I.", "answer": "[set(), {'O'}, {'U'}, {'H'}, {'Q'}, {'J'}, {'F'}, {'O', 'U'}, {'H', 'O'}, {'Q', 'O'}, {'J', 'O'}, {'F', 'O'}, {'H', 'U'}, {'Q', 'U'}, {'J', 'U'}, {'H', 'Q'}, {'J', 'H'}, {'F', 'H'}, {'J', 'Q'}, {'F', 'Q'}, {'J', 'F'}, {'H', 'O', 'U'}, {'Q', 'O', 'U'}, {'J', 'O', 'U'}, {'F', 'O', 'U'}, {'H', 'Q', 'O'}, {'J', 'H', 'O'}, {'F', 'H', 'O'}, {'J', 'Q', 'O'}, {'F', 'Q', 'O'}, {'J', 'F', 'O'}, {'H', 'Q', 'U'}, {'J', 'H', 'U'}, {'F', 'H', 'U'}, {'J', 'Q', 'U'}, {'J', 'F', 'U'}, {'J', 'H', 'Q'}, {'F', 'H', 'Q'}, {'J', 'F', 'H'}, {'J', 'F', 'Q'}, {'H', 'Q', 'O', 'U'}, {'J', 'H', 'O', 'U'}, {'F', 'H', 'O', 'U'}, {'J', 'Q', 'O', 'U'}, {'F', 'Q', 'O', 'U'}, {'J', 'F', 'O', 'U'}, {'J', 'H', 'Q', 'O'}, {'F', 'H', 'Q', 'O'}, {'J', 'F', 'H', 'O'}, {'J', 'F', 'Q', 'O'}, {'J', 'H', 'Q', 'U'}, {'F', 'H', 'Q', 'U'}, {'J', 'F', 'H', 'U'}, {'J', 'F', 'Q', 'U'}, {'J', 'F', 'H', 'Q'}, {'O', 'U', 'H', 'Q', 'J'}, {'O', 'U', 'H', 'Q', 'F'}, {'O', 'U', 'H', 'J', 'F'}, {'O', 'U', 'Q', 'J', 'F'}, {'O', 'H', 'Q', 'J', 'F'}, {'U', 'H', 'Q', 'J', 'F'}, {'O', 'U', 'H', 'Q', 'J', 'F'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes J, H, O, F, Q, U, K, I, directed edges F->K, J->F, O->F, K->I, O->U, H->O, J->K, J->U, J->Q and bi-directed edges F<->I, H<->K, F<->Q, J<->U, H<->F.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13672825", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path K<-J<->U<-O<-H<->F<->I.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes J, H, O, F, Q, U, K, I, directed edges F->K, J->F, O->F, K->I, O->U, H->O, J->K, J->U, J->Q and bi-directed edges F<->I, H<->K, F<->Q, J<->U, H<->F.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13672825", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path F<->H->O->U<-J->K be blocked by nodeset {'I', 'Q'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes J, H, O, F, Q, U, K, I, directed edges F->K, J->F, O->F, K->I, O->U, H->O, J->K, J->U, J->Q and bi-directed edges F<->I, H<->K, F<->Q, J<->U, H<->F.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13672825", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path J->U<-O<-H<->F<->I<-K?\nA. {'I', 'U'}\nB. {'F', 'Q', 'O', 'U'}\nC. {'I', 'F', 'U'}\nD. {'I', 'Q', 'U'}", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes R, J, U, S, B, L, H, D, directed edges J->D, J->U, R->H, U->L, R->S, L->D, U->D, B->H, J->H, B->D and bi-directed edges U<->D, R<->J, J<->H, R<->S.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "65496000", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path J<->R->H<-B->D<->U->L.", "answer": "[set(), {'D'}, {'S'}, {'B'}, {'U'}, {'H'}, {'R'}, {'D', 'S'}, {'D', 'B'}, {'D', 'U'}, {'D', 'R'}, {'S', 'B'}, {'S', 'U'}, {'H', 'S'}, {'S', 'R'}, {'B', 'U'}, {'H', 'B'}, {'R', 'B'}, {'H', 'U'}, {'R', 'U'}, {'H', 'R'}, {'D', 'S', 'B'}, {'D', 'S', 'U'}, {'D', 'S', 'R'}, {'D', 'B', 'U'}, {'D', 'H', 'B'}, {'D', 'R', 'B'}, {'D', 'H', 'U'}, {'D', 'R', 'U'}, {'D', 'H', 'R'}, {'S', 'B', 'U'}, {'H', 'S', 'B'}, {'S', 'R', 'B'}, {'H', 'S', 'U'}, {'S', 'R', 'U'}, {'H', 'S', 'R'}, {'H', 'B', 'U'}, {'R', 'B', 'U'}, {'H', 'R', 'B'}, {'H', 'R', 'U'}, {'D', 'S', 'B', 'U'}, {'D', 'H', 'S', 'B'}, {'D', 'S', 'R', 'B'}, {'D', 'H', 'S', 'U'}, {'D', 'S', 'R', 'U'}, {'D', 'H', 'S', 'R'}, {'D', 'H', 'B', 'U'}, {'D', 'R', 'B', 'U'}, {'D', 'H', 'R', 'B'}, {'D', 'H', 'R', 'U'}, {'H', 'S', 'B', 'U'}, {'S', 'R', 'B', 'U'}, {'H', 'S', 'R', 'B'}, {'H', 'S', 'R', 'U'}, {'H', 'R', 'B', 'U'}, {'D', 'S', 'B', 'U', 'H'}, {'D', 'S', 'B', 'U', 'R'}, {'D', 'S', 'B', 'H', 'R'}, {'D', 'S', 'U', 'H', 'R'}, {'D', 'B', 'U', 'H', 'R'}, {'S', 'B', 'U', 'H', 'R'}, {'D', 'S', 'B', 'U', 'H', 'R'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes R, J, U, S, B, L, H, D, directed edges J->D, J->U, R->H, U->L, R->S, L->D, U->D, B->H, J->H, B->D and bi-directed edges U<->D, R<->J, J<->H, R<->S.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "65496000", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path J<->R->H<-B->D<->U->L.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes R, J, U, S, B, L, H, D, directed edges J->D, J->U, R->H, U->L, R->S, L->D, U->D, B->H, J->H, B->D and bi-directed edges U<->D, R<->J, J<->H, R<->S.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "65496000", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path B->H<->J->U<->D be blocked by nodeset {'L', 'S', 'R', 'U'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes R, J, U, S, B, L, H, D, directed edges J->D, J->U, R->H, U->L, R->S, L->D, U->D, B->H, J->H, B->D and bi-directed edges U<->D, R<->J, J<->H, R<->S.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "65496000", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path J->H<-B->D?\nA. {'H', 'S', 'U'}\nB. {'S', 'B', 'U'}\nC. {'H', 'L', 'R'}\nD. {'H'}", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes C, X, I, H, F, V, A, Y, Q, directed edges I->F, X->H, X->Y, C->A, H->F, X->Q, C->F, C->Y, I->Y, F->Q, H->V and bi-directed edges H<->V, X<->H, X<->F, H<->Q, F<->Y, C<->A.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13708323", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path X<->F<-H->V.", "answer": "[set(), {'I'}, {'A'}, {'H'}, {'C'}, {'Y'}, {'I', 'A'}, {'I', 'H'}, {'I', 'C'}, {'I', 'Y'}, {'H', 'A'}, {'C', 'A'}, {'A', 'Y'}, {'H', 'Q'}, {'F', 'H'}, {'H', 'C'}, {'H', 'Y'}, {'C', 'Y'}, {'I', 'H', 'A'}, {'I', 'C', 'A'}, {'I', 'A', 'Y'}, {'I', 'H', 'Q'}, {'F', 'I', 'H'}, {'I', 'H', 'C'}, {'I', 'H', 'Y'}, {'I', 'C', 'Y'}, {'H', 'A', 'Q'}, {'F', 'H', 'A'}, {'H', 'C', 'A'}, {'H', 'A', 'Y'}, {'C', 'A', 'Y'}, {'F', 'H', 'Q'}, {'H', 'C', 'Q'}, {'H', 'Q', 'Y'}, {'F', 'H', 'C'}, {'F', 'H', 'Y'}, {'H', 'C', 'Y'}, {'I', 'H', 'A', 'Q'}, {'F', 'I', 'H', 'A'}, {'I', 'H', 'C', 'A'}, {'I', 'H', 'A', 'Y'}, {'I', 'C', 'A', 'Y'}, {'F', 'I', 'H', 'Q'}, {'I', 'H', 'C', 'Q'}, {'I', 'H', 'Q', 'Y'}, {'F', 'I', 'H', 'C'}, {'F', 'I', 'H', 'Y'}, {'I', 'H', 'C', 'Y'}, {'F', 'H', 'A', 'Q'}, {'H', 'C', 'A', 'Q'}, {'H', 'A', 'Q', 'Y'}, {'F', 'H', 'C', 'A'}, {'F', 'H', 'A', 'Y'}, {'H', 'C', 'A', 'Y'}, {'F', 'H', 'C', 'Q'}, {'F', 'H', 'Q', 'Y'}, {'H', 'C', 'Q', 'Y'}, {'F', 'H', 'C', 'Y'}, {'I', 'A', 'H', 'Q', 'F'}, {'I', 'A', 'H', 'Q', 'C'}, {'I', 'A', 'H', 'Q', 'Y'}, {'I', 'A', 'H', 'F', 'C'}, {'I', 'A', 'H', 'F', 'Y'}, {'I', 'A', 'H', 'C', 'Y'}, {'I', 'H', 'Q', 'F', 'C'}, {'I', 'H', 'Q', 'F', 'Y'}, {'I', 'H', 'Q', 'C', 'Y'}, {'I', 'H', 'F', 'C', 'Y'}, {'A', 'H', 'Q', 'F', 'C'}, {'A', 'H', 'Q', 'F', 'Y'}, {'A', 'H', 'Q', 'C', 'Y'}, {'A', 'H', 'F', 'C', 'Y'}, {'H', 'Q', 'F', 'C', 'Y'}, {'I', 'A', 'H', 'Q', 'F', 'C'}, {'I', 'A', 'H', 'Q', 'F', 'Y'}, {'I', 'A', 'H', 'Q', 'C', 'Y'}, {'I', 'A', 'H', 'F', 'C', 'Y'}, {'I', 'H', 'Q', 'F', 'C', 'Y'}, {'A', 'H', 'Q', 'F', 'C', 'Y'}, {'I', 'A', 'H', 'Q', 'F', 'C', 'Y'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes C, X, I, H, F, V, A, Y, Q, directed edges I->F, X->H, X->Y, C->A, H->F, X->Q, C->F, C->Y, I->Y, F->Q, H->V and bi-directed edges H<->V, X<->H, X<->F, H<->Q, F<->Y, C<->A.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13708323", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path X<->F<-H->V.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes C, X, I, H, F, V, A, Y, Q, directed edges I->F, X->H, X->Y, C->A, H->F, X->Q, C->F, C->Y, I->Y, F->Q, H->V and bi-directed edges H<->V, X<->H, X<->F, H<->Q, F<->Y, C<->A.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13708323", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path H<->Q<-X->Y<-I->F be blocked by nodeset {'X', 'V', 'I', 'Q'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes C, X, I, H, F, V, A, Y, Q, directed edges I->F, X->H, X->Y, C->A, H->F, X->Q, C->F, C->Y, I->Y, F->Q, H->V and bi-directed edges H<->V, X<->H, X<->F, H<->Q, F<->Y, C<->A.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "13708323", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path C->F->Q<-X->Y?\nA. {'I', 'A', 'H', 'V', 'Q'}\nB. {'V', 'I', 'Q'}\nC. {'V', 'I', 'A', 'Q'}\nD. {'X', 'V', 'H', 'Q'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, P, J, R, S, L, T, O, E, directed edges J->L, J->T, L->O, P->R, S->O, R->T, K->J, S->L, P->E, L->T, K->O, P->O and bi-directed edges S<->O, J<->R, P<->S, P<->R, K<->S, O<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44525380", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path K->J<->R<-P->E<->O<-S->L->T.", "answer": "[set(), {'S'}, {'O'}, {'P'}, {'R'}, {'J'}, {'L'}, {'E'}, {'S', 'O'}, {'P', 'S'}, {'S', 'R'}, {'J', 'S'}, {'L', 'S'}, {'S', 'E'}, {'P', 'O'}, {'R', 'O'}, {'J', 'O'}, {'L', 'O'}, {'E', 'O'}, {'P', 'R'}, {'P', 'J'}, {'P', 'L'}, {'P', 'E'}, {'J', 'R'}, {'L', 'R'}, {'E', 'R'}, {'J', 'L'}, {'J', 'E'}, {'L', 'E'}, {'P', 'S', 'O'}, {'S', 'R', 'O'}, {'J', 'S', 'O'}, {'L', 'S', 'O'}, {'S', 'E', 'O'}, {'P', 'S', 'R'}, {'P', 'J', 'S'}, {'P', 'L', 'S'}, {'P', 'S', 'E'}, {'J', 'S', 'R'}, {'L', 'S', 'R'}, {'S', 'E', 'R'}, {'J', 'L', 'S'}, {'J', 'S', 'E'}, {'L', 'S', 'E'}, {'P', 'R', 'O'}, {'P', 'J', 'O'}, {'P', 'L', 'O'}, {'P', 'E', 'O'}, {'J', 'R', 'O'}, {'L', 'R', 'O'}, {'J', 'L', 'O'}, {'J', 'E', 'O'}, {'L', 'E', 'O'}, {'P', 'J', 'R'}, {'P', 'L', 'R'}, {'P', 'E', 'R'}, {'P', 'J', 'L'}, {'P', 'J', 'E'}, {'P', 'L', 'E'}, {'J', 'L', 'R'}, {'J', 'E', 'R'}, {'L', 'E', 'R'}, {'J', 'L', 'E'}, {'P', 'S', 'R', 'O'}, {'P', 'J', 'S', 'O'}, {'P', 'L', 'S', 'O'}, {'P', 'S', 'E', 'O'}, {'J', 'S', 'R', 'O'}, {'L', 'S', 'R', 'O'}, {'E', 'S', 'R', 'O'}, {'J', 'L', 'S', 'O'}, {'J', 'S', 'E', 'O'}, {'L', 'S', 'E', 'O'}, {'P', 'J', 'S', 'R'}, {'P', 'L', 'S', 'R'}, {'P', 'S', 'E', 'R'}, {'P', 'J', 'L', 'S'}, {'P', 'J', 'S', 'E'}, {'P', 'L', 'S', 'E'}, {'J', 'L', 'S', 'R'}, {'J', 'S', 'E', 'R'}, {'L', 'S', 'E', 'R'}, {'J', 'L', 'S', 'E'}, {'P', 'J', 'R', 'O'}, {'P', 'L', 'R', 'O'}, {'P', 'E', 'R', 'O'}, {'P', 'J', 'L', 'O'}, {'P', 'J', 'E', 'O'}, {'P', 'L', 'E', 'O'}, {'J', 'L', 'R', 'O'}, {'E', 'L', 'R', 'O'}, {'J', 'L', 'E', 'O'}, {'P', 'J', 'L', 'R'}, {'P', 'J', 'E', 'R'}, {'P', 'L', 'E', 'R'}, {'P', 'J', 'L', 'E'}, {'J', 'L', 'E', 'R'}, {'S', 'O', 'P', 'J', 'R'}, {'S', 'O', 'P', 'L', 'R'}, {'S', 'O', 'P', 'R', 'E'}, {'S', 'O', 'P', 'J', 'L'}, {'S', 'O', 'P', 'J', 'E'}, {'S', 'O', 'P', 'L', 'E'}, {'S', 'O', 'J', 'L', 'R'}, {'S', 'O', 'R', 'J', 'E'}, {'S', 'O', 'R', 'L', 'E'}, {'S', 'O', 'J', 'L', 'E'}, {'S', 'P', 'J', 'L', 'R'}, {'S', 'P', 'R', 'J', 'E'}, {'S', 'P', 'R', 'L', 'E'}, {'S', 'P', 'J', 'L', 'E'}, {'S', 'R', 'J', 'L', 'E'}, {'O', 'P', 'J', 'L', 'R'}, {'O', 'P', 'R', 'J', 'E'}, {'O', 'P', 'R', 'L', 'E'}, {'O', 'P', 'J', 'L', 'E'}, {'O', 'R', 'J', 'L', 'E'}, {'P', 'R', 'J', 'L', 'E'}, {'S', 'O', 'P', 'J', 'L', 'R'}, {'S', 'O', 'P', 'E', 'J', 'R'}, {'S', 'O', 'P', 'E', 'L', 'R'}, {'S', 'O', 'P', 'J', 'L', 'E'}, {'S', 'O', 'E', 'J', 'L', 'R'}, {'S', 'P', 'E', 'J', 'L', 'R'}, {'O', 'P', 'E', 'J', 'L', 'R'}, {'S', 'O', 'P', 'E', 'J', 'L', 'R'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, P, J, R, S, L, T, O, E, directed edges J->L, J->T, L->O, P->R, S->O, R->T, K->J, S->L, P->E, L->T, K->O, P->O and bi-directed edges S<->O, J<->R, P<->S, P<->R, K<->S, O<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44525380", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path K->J<->R<-P->E<->O<-S->L->T.", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, P, J, R, S, L, T, O, E, directed edges J->L, J->T, L->O, P->R, S->O, R->T, K->J, S->L, P->E, L->T, K->O, P->O and bi-directed edges S<->O, J<->R, P<->S, P<->R, K<->S, O<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44525380", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path P<->R<->J->L<-S<->O<->E be blocked by nodeset {'T', 'O'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, P, J, R, S, L, T, O, E, directed edges J->L, J->T, L->O, P->R, S->O, R->T, K->J, S->L, P->E, L->T, K->O, P->O and bi-directed edges S<->O, J<->R, P<->S, P<->R, K<->S, O<->E.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "44525380", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path L<-S->O?\nA. {'J', 'T', 'R', 'K'}\nB. {'T', 'E', 'R', 'K'}\nC. {'P', 'R', 'K'}\nD. {'S', 'K', 'P', 'J', 'E'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, G, K, Z, C, T, B, R, D, directed edges K->C, K->T, Q->D, G->D, K->D, K->R, Q->G, K->Z, Q->B and bi-directed edges Z<->R, Z<->C, B<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "57314426", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can block path Q->G->D.", "answer": "[{'G'}, {'G', 'Z'}, {'G', 'B'}, {'G', 'K'}, {'G', 'T'}, {'G', 'C'}, {'G', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B'}, {'G', 'Z', 'K'}, {'G', 'Z', 'T'}, {'G', 'Z', 'C'}, {'G', 'Z', 'R'}, {'G', 'B', 'K'}, {'G', 'T', 'B'}, {'G', 'C', 'B'}, {'G', 'R', 'B'}, {'G', 'T', 'K'}, {'G', 'C', 'K'}, {'G', 'R', 'K'}, {'G', 'T', 'C'}, {'G', 'T', 'R'}, {'G', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B', 'K'}, {'G', 'Z', 'T', 'B'}, {'G', 'Z', 'C', 'B'}, {'G', 'Z', 'R', 'B'}, {'G', 'Z', 'T', 'K'}, {'G', 'Z', 'C', 'K'}, {'G', 'Z', 'R', 'K'}, {'G', 'Z', 'C', 'T'}, {'G', 'Z', 'T', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'T', 'B', 'K'}, {'G', 'C', 'B', 'K'}, {'G', 'R', 'B', 'K'}, {'G', 'T', 'C', 'B'}, {'G', 'T', 'R', 'B'}, {'G', 'C', 'R', 'B'}, {'G', 'T', 'C', 'K'}, {'G', 'T', 'R', 'K'}, {'G', 'C', 'R', 'K'}, {'G', 'T', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B', 'K', 'T'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B', 'K', 'C'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B', 'K', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B', 'T', 'C'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B', 'T', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'K', 'T', 'C'}, {'G', 'Z', 'K', 'T', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'K', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'T', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'B', 'K', 'T', 'C'}, {'G', 'B', 'K', 'T', 'R'}, {'G', 'B', 'K', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'B', 'T', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'K', 'T', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B', 'K', 'T', 'C'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B', 'K', 'T', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B', 'K', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B', 'T', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'K', 'T', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'B', 'K', 'T', 'C', 'R'}, {'G', 'Z', 'B', 'K', 'T', 'C', 'R'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, G, K, Z, C, T, B, R, D, directed edges K->C, K->T, Q->D, G->D, K->D, K->R, Q->G, K->Z, Q->B and bi-directed edges Z<->R, Z<->C, B<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "57314426", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can block path Q->G->D.", "answer": "{'G'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, G, K, Z, C, T, B, R, D, directed edges K->C, K->T, Q->D, G->D, K->D, K->R, Q->G, K->Z, Q->B and bi-directed edges Z<->R, Z<->C, B<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "57314426", "sid": 2, "question": "Can path K->Z<->C be blocked by nodeset {'D', 'G', 'Z', 'B', 'Q', 'R'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, G, K, Z, C, T, B, R, D, directed edges K->C, K->T, Q->D, G->D, K->D, K->R, Q->G, K->Z, Q->B and bi-directed edges Z<->R, Z<->C, B<->D.", "graph_type": "ADMG", "uid": "57314426", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can block path Q->B<->D?\nA. {'Z', 'C', 'T'}\nB. {'T', 'R', 'B'}\nC. {'G', 'T', 'C', 'B'}\nD. {'C', 'R', 'B', 'K'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "blocked_path"}
